https://journallife.me/privacy-policy/

JOURNALLIFE PRIVACY POLICY
THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME, INFORMS YOU WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED AND USED ON THIS LIFEJOURNAL.COM WEBSITE (“SITE”). By accessing or attempting to interact with any part of the Site, you agree that you have read, understand and agree to this Privacy Policy, and you consent to the data collection and use practices described in this policy whether you are or are not a registered user, or a visitor just browsing the Site. This Privacy Policy applies only to this websites and not to any third-party websites that may be accessed through hyper-links on this website.
Users can access limited features of the Site without disclosing personal information. In order to access the entire website or use its journaling features, users must register for an account, which will provide the registrant with full access to the Site, including access to any website’s forums or message boards or online classrooms.
1. COLLECTED INFORMATION
A. Information Sought During Registration.
During the account registration process, you will be asked to submit personal information, including a user name and at least one active e-mail address. You also may be requested to provide information necessary to process any payment due to establish a paid account. Additionally, you may have the opportunity to subscribe to Site newsletters regarding and to receive information about Chronicles Software’s products, services and special offers or events.
B. Information Sought During Website Contests.
In the event the Site offers any contests, personal information may be collected with the sole purpose of notifying you if you win the contest.
C. Automatically Collected Information.
Information concerning your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected and may be used by Chronicles Software for use with other Chronicles Software products and services. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, pages accessed, access times and referring website addresses. Chronicles Software uses this information to maintain and improve the quality of its service and to
provide general statistics about Site visitors.
We also may track the pages on this website that visitors access in order to deliver customized content and advertising within the Site to visitors whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area and to evaluate future modification to the functionality of the Site.
D. Storage and Transfer of Personally Identifiable Information.
Chronicles Software may store and process in the United States or any other country in which Chronicles Software or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. By using Chronicles Software’s websites, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not sell, rent, trade, or lease this
2. INFORMATION SECURITY
We secure the e-mail address you provide and content you post in journal entries on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. All information transmitted between you and the Site uses SSL/HTTPS encrypted communication between you and our servers.
You must keep your password confidential and you must not share this information with anyone. If you share a computer with anyone, you should always log out of the website before leaving it to prevent access to your information from subsequent users of that computer.
3. SHARING OF INFORMATION
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use of the Site, the personal registration information (e.g. email address, browser type) you provide on this site will not be shared with any third-parties, although we reserve the right, as needed, to share such information with our affiliates and agents without your permission in order to provide, maintain, and improve your customer experience.
We sometime hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as sending newsletters, providing customer service, and performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies with the information that they need to provide us with such services, and we prohibit them from using that information for any other purpose.
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Chronicles Software or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Chronicles Software or one of Chronicles Software’s websites; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site, or the general public. BY ACCEPTING THIS AGREEMENT YOU WAIVE AND HOLD HARMLESS CHRONICLES SOFTWARE FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN BY CHRONICLES SOFTWARE DURING OR AS A RESULT OF ITS INVESTIGATIONS AND/OR FROM ANY ACTIONS TAKEN AS A CONSEQUENCE OF INVESTIGATIONS BY EITHER CHRONICLES SOFTWARE OR LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES.
4. USE OF COOKIES
We use cookies to assist you with making your online experience more individualized. A cookie is a text file that is placed on the hard disk of your computer by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies are used for convenience and to save you time when you next visit this website. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page, so that when you visit the site again, the experience will be personalized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to set your computer to accept cookies from this website, you may also choose to be logged into the site automatically. If you choose to
decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this website or the other websites that you visit and you may experience technical problems receiving current information from such cookie-disabled websites.
5. USE OF WEB BEACONS
The Site may contain electronic images known as web beacons – also referred to as single-pixel gifs – that permit Chronicles Software (including its affiliates and service providers) to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics – (e.g., recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). Web beacons are not used to access your personal information on the Site; they are solely used to compile aggregated statistics concerning the use of the Site. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, the time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides.
6. FORUMS OFFERED ON THIS SITE
While Account holder journal entries and journal data are private, password-protected, encrypted, and secure and not publically available , any personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data that you disclose through the any public online forums hosted on the Site (e.g. for tech support), may be collected and used by others. We recommend caution when giving out personal information to others in these public online forums.
Additionally, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to visit via hyperlinks posted on this website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on third-party websites accessed through the Site.
7. USER ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OF INFORMATION
You can access some of the information that we collect and process about you. For example, you can access information regarding your Account subscription; your personally identifiable information (including user identification, e-mail, password, communications preferences; payment settings (including credit card information); and e-mail notification settings. With respect to your communications preferences, you can unsubscribe from newsletters by following the instructions included in the newsletter you receive. If your e-mail address has changed and you would like to continue to receive newsletters, you will need to access your account and update your e-mail address information in your account and sign-up again for the newsletter. Occasionally, we will send out e-mails concerning Site disruptions, new products and other news about Chronicles Software’s products and services. These e-mails are sent to all account holders and are not subscription-based. Such e-mails are considered a part of Chronicles Software’s service to the users of its website.
8. CHILDREN
If you are under 18, you may use this website only through your parent or guardian and you are unable to purchase products from this website, unless such purchase is made through an adult. Absolutely no children under 13 may use this website’s journaling features or any other portion of the website which may require the submission of personally identifiable information.
9. CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS
By visiting this website, you accept that your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of the law of the state of Florida. If you have any concern about privacy issues, please contact us as directed in this Policy.
10. CONTACT INFORMATION
We welcome feedback regarding this Privacy Policy. If at any time you believe that this website has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. E-mail should be sent to info@lifejournal.com.
WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, FROM TIME TO TIME, WITH OR WITHOUT NOTICE TO YOU, TO MAKE CHANGES TO THIS POLICY IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION. CONTINUED USE OF ANY PART OF THIS WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES. THE MOST CURRENT VERSION OF THESE POLICIES, WHICH SUPERCEDES ALL PREVIOUS VERSIONS, CAN BE REVIEWED BY CLICKING ON THE “PRIVACY POLICY” HYPERLINK LOCATED AT THE BOTTOM OF EVERY PAGE ON THE SITE.
Last updated January 11, 2013
More Information
Expert Endorsements
Customer Reviews
JL Windows Help Videos
JournalLife Blog
Support
Customer Support
© 2012 - 2020, Dragonfly Research Group, LLC. All rights reserved.
